Grounded for Christmas is a romance, tv movie film directed by Amyn Kaderali.
When a winter storm hits Cleveland and grounds flights, the nearby
hotels quickly fill up with stranded travelers.
Nina, a pilot, reluctantly agrees to let her arrogant but charming
fellow pilot, Brady, stay at her nearby parents' home.
But when they discover her family is hosting a tree trimming party that night and that
her ex will be there, Brady pretends to be her boyfriend to help her out.
Nina, played by Julianna Guill.
Brady, played by Corey Sevier.
Susan, played by Cheryl Ladd.
Bert, played by Ted Atherton.
Marcy, played by Paula Brancati.
Will, played by Jacob Blair.
A Very Jonas Christmas Movie is a 2025 American Christmas musical comedy film
directed by Jessica Yu and written by Isaac Aptaker and Elizabeth Berger.
It stars the Jonas Brothers (Kevin Jonas, Joe Jonas,
and Nick Jonas) and Chloe Bennet.
The film was released on Disney+ and Hulu on November 14, 2025.
It received positive reviews from critics, with particular praise
directed at the music and the chemistry of the Jonas Brothers.
The tone is emotional.